grotal.com 2019-05-25

# Privacy Policy

Grotal Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We understand your concern about the personal information you submit on Grotal.com and our responsibility to protect your privacy. As part of this responsibility, we assure that we will not misuse your personal information in any way.

This document highlights every aspect of the Privacy Policy to you. Your visit and actions undertaken on our site will be governed by the following policy. This policy provides the manner your data is collected and used by Grotal.com. You are advised to please read the policy. By accessing the services provided by Grotal.com, you agree to the collection and use of your data by Grotal.com. We reserve the right to add, modify, delete or change the contents of this privacy policy as may be felt necessary by us.

## Information Collected

In order to use the Grotal.com service, you must establish an account with us. During the registration process, we require entry of Personal Information such as your name, e-mail address, and mobile number. Information about you may also be used to notify you about functionality changes on our website, new services and special offers.

## Information Modification

Grotal.com is committed to ensuring that you have appropriate control over your information. You can modify your personal information by accessing the ‘Edit’ option anytime from our site.

If you are no longer an account holder and you would like to delete your Personal Information, you can send an e-mail request to us. Your Personal Information will be deleted unless we are under a legal obligation to retain it.

## Information Sharing

We do not rent, sell, or give away your information to anyone. To some extent, information has to be passed on to the law authorities, for fraud detection, and for the safety of our site, employees, management, users, members and other affiliates associated with us.

## Third Party ad Networks

By using grotal you agree and accept that third party ad networks that are serving ads on grotal.com may be placing and reading cookies on your browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving.

##  Rate Change 

New rates are effective from 1st march every year, and will reflect to all. The deductions from 1st march will be as per new rates. The rate can be less or greater than previous rates depending up on visitors of the grotal.com

## Contacting Grotal.com

If you have questions about our privacy policy or anything related to your privacy on our service, we'd love to hear from you.  
Feel free to contact us at : **+91 - 9914778899**

 **Email: info@grotal.com**
